欢迎光临Air House77超级影院！！！
Welcome to Air House Cinemas
祝您观影愉快！
Please enjoy the movie!
✓爪子巡逻 爪子巡逻∮
♪ PAW Patrol, PAW Patrol ♪
✓喷气式飞机救援⏹
♪ Jet to the rescue ♪
每当需要的时候♫
♪ Whenever they are needed ♪
\当事情看起来很艰难的时候
\h\h\h♪ When things are looking tough ♪
✓小狗们飞走来拯救这一天∮
♪ The pups take flight to save \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hthe day ♪
✓超音速方式♫
♪ The super sonic way ♪
›蔡斯 马歇尔♫
♪ Chase, Marshall ♪
✓碎石 祖玛♫
♪ Rubble, Zuma ♪
“洛基 珠穆朗玛峰”
♪ Rocky, Everest ♪
›跟踪器 斯凯♫
♪ Tracker, Skye ♪
✓当幼崽飞起来的时候 没有任何高度太高的地方♫
♪ There’s no height too high \h\h\h\hwhen the pups fly ♪
✓爪子巡逻统治天空⏹
♪ PAW Patrol rules the sky ♪
✓所以抬头看 \h\h\hPAW Patrol⏹
♪ So look up high, \h\h\hPAW Patrol ♪
✓喷气式飞机去救小狗♫
♪ Jet To The Rescue Pups ♪
♪
你们第一次来巴金堡怎么样 伙计们？
SKYE: What do you think of Barkingburg on your first visit, guys?
珠穆朗玛峰：太棒了！
EVEREST: It's amazing!
跟踪器 看看那些老建筑！
Tracker, look at all those old buildings!
这座城市是马尼菲科！
The city is magnífico!
（时钟响得很响）
(Clock ringing loudly)
它甚至听起来很棒！
It even sounds magnificent!
现在你能告诉我们最大的惊喜是什么吗 莱德？
Now can you tell us what the big surprise is, Ryder?
是的 告诉我们！拜托！
Yeah, tell us! Please!
来吧 莱德！告诉我们 伙计！
Come on, Ryder! Tell us, dude!
好吧 小狗们 既然我们来了
Okay, pups. Now that we're here,
我可以播放公主给你的重要信息
I can play you this important message from the Princess.
对莱德和爪子巡逻队来说 你是我唯一的希望
To Ryder and the PAW Patrol,  you're my only hope.
我迫切需要你来巴金堡城堡
I urgently need you to come to  Barkingburg Castle...
（气喘吁吁地说）
(All gasping)
加入我的皇家生日派对！
To join me for my royal  birthday party!
生日派对？！
A birthday party?!
太酷了！当铺！
So cool! Pawesome!
酷！耶！
Cool! Yay!
（小狗欢呼 嚎叫）
(Pups cheering, howling)
耶 我们到了！
Yay, we're here!
呜呜！派对时间！
Whoo-hoo! Party time!
女士们 先生们 现在请殿下
Ladies and gentlemen, I present Her Royal Highness,
巴金堡公主！
the Princess of Barkingburg!
（人群欢呼 鼓掌）
(Crowd cheering, applauding)
谢谢大家来参加我的聚会
Thank you all for coming to my party.
厄尔 请宣布我的特别朋友
Earl, please announce my special friends.
首先 可爱的 可爱的
First up, the lovable, adorable,
真是高贵的皇家小猫！
positively regal Royal Kittens!
亨利和伊丽莎白
Henry and Elizabeth.
（鼓掌）
(Applauding)
小猫在我面前？！
Kittens before me?!
皇室的小狗 宝贝
The Royal Pup, Sweetie.
更像是这样
That's more like it.
（擤鼻涕）
(Blowing nose)
巴金堡人--
People of Barkingburg--
厄尔：莱德！还有爪子巡逻队！
EARL: Ryder! And the PAW Patrol!
（人群欢呼）
(Crowd cheering)
嘿 我想他们喜欢我们！
Hey, I think they like us!
是啊 我真的能感受到爱
Yeah, I can really feel the love.
布兹比！他们为爪子巡逻队欢呼得更大声了
Buzby! They're cheering louder for the PAW Patrol
比他们为我做的还要多 当我是女王的时候
than they did for me. When I'm queen,
我将是唯一的小狗人们欢呼！
I'll be the only pup people cheer for!
所有人：生日快乐 公主！
ALL: Happy Birthday, Princess!
费利兹·卡姆贝雷迪诺斯 王子！
Feliz cumpleaños, Princesa!
谢谢你 追踪器！
Muchas gracias, Tracker!
康诺卡罗酒店！很高兴见到你
Encantada de conocerlo! I'm delighted to meet you.
你听到了吗？她很高兴见到我！
Did you hear that? She's glad to meet me!
（咯咯笑）
(Giggling)
你一定是珠穆朗玛峰！
And you must be Everest!
我听说你在冰上或雪地上勇敢地营救--
I've heard of your many daring rescues on ice or snow--
我准备好了！
I'm ready to go!
我们为您准备了一个特别的惊喜 殿下
We have a special surprise planned for you, Your Highness.
聚会后我们会给你的
We'll give it to you after the party.
我等不及了！我喜欢惊喜！（开门）
I can't wait! I love surprises! (Doors opening)
你好 巴金堡！
Hello, Barkingburg!
我希望我参加聚会不会太晚！
I hope I'm not too late for the party!
请你通知我好吗？我是--
Would you please announce me? I'm--
（窃窃私语）
(Whispering)
弗拉金顿公爵！
The Duke of Flappington!
什么？弗拉金顿公爵？
What? The Duke of Flappington?
那在哪儿？我从没听说过
Where's that? I've never heard of it.
嗯 我在邀请名单上没看到他的名字
Hm, I didn't see his name on the invitation list.
生日快乐 表弟！
Happy Birthday, cousin!
我不知道我有个表弟
I didn't know I had a cousin.
是的 殿下 他来自这个家族的一个遥远的分支
Yes, Your Highness. He's from a distant branch of the family.
很高兴见到你 堂兄 亚平顿公爵！
Well, it's a pleasure to meet you, cousin, Duke of Yappington!
（大笑）
(Laughing)
那是弗拉金顿 离这儿只有很短的距离 缩放！
That's Flappington. It's just a short flight away. Zoom!
嗯 你穿的是飞行员制服吗？
Hm, is that a pilot's uniform you're wearing?
它是！我是个优秀的飞行员 如果可以的话 我会住在天上！
It is! I'm an excellent flyer. I'd live in the sky if I could!
你也是飞行员？我总是“准备”去见另一个传单！
You're a pilot too? I'm always "up" for meeting another flyer!
（鸟叫）啊！一只鹰！
(Bird screeching) Augh! An eagle!
（惊恐地喊道）
(Shouting in panic)
莱德：小狗们 保护公主！
RYDER: Pups, protect the Princess!
别害怕
Don't be afraid.
这只是我的宠物鹰 珍爪！呱呱叫？
It's just my pet eagle, Jean-Clawed! Caw-cah-caw?
（尖叫声）
(Squawking)
呱呱 呱呱 呱呱 呱呱！（吱吱声）
Caw, caw, cah-caw, caw! (Squeaking)
哦 真是松了一口气
Oh, what a relief.
你还好吧 斯凯？
Are you okay, Skye?
我很好 我只是很害怕老鹰
I'm fine, I'm just really afraid of eagles.
别害怕 我自己训练的
Don't be frightened, I trained him myself.
琼用爪子抓着 向公主鞠躬
Jean-Clawed, bow to the Princess.
♪
你的举止真有风度啊 琼·克劳奇说
What charming manners you have, Jean-Clawed.
（喇叭声）
(Trumpet sounding)
哦 殿下
Oh, Your Highness,
是时候接受你的皇家生日礼物了！
it's time to receive your royal birthday present!
皇室的礼物？可能是什么？
A royal present? What could it be?
巴金堡伯爵！
The Earl of Barkingburg!
这是典当行的安全功能！
That's a pawesome security feature!
只有伯爵的声音才能关闭激光束
Only the Earl's voice can turn off the laser beams.
我给你
I give you...
巴金堡的宝石！
the Gem of Barkingburg!
哇 太棒了！
Whoa, it's amazing!
闪亮的
Shiny.
就在这里
There it is.
谢谢你 厄尔 它很漂亮
Thank you, Earl. It's beautiful.
为什么我以前没见过这个？
Why haven't I seen this before?
因为它只给未来的国王或王后--
Because it's only given to the future king or queen--
当他们十岁的时候！
When they reach the age of ten!
这些皇家习俗通常都是这样的
Is how these royal customs usually go.
布兹比 如果我有那颗宝石 我会是未来的女王！
Buzby, if I had that gem, I'd be the future queen!
（喇叭声）
(Trumpet sounding)
啊 殿下 这意味着是时候了
Ah, Your Highness, that means it's time
给你切生日蛋糕
for you to cut your birthday cake.
我待会再试试宝石
I'll try the gem on later.
大家跟我到宴会厅去！
Follow me to the banquet hall, everyone!
（嘉宾欢呼）
(Guests cheering)
♪
现在是我拿宝石的机会了 布兹比！
Now's my chance to take the gem, Buzby!
现在是我拿宝石的机会了 珍爪！
Now's my chance to take the gem, Jean-Clawed!
哦！
Oof!
（尖叫声）
(Squawking)
（嘟嘟声）
(Beeping)
你在皇家金库干什么 公爵夫人？
What are you doing by the royal vault, your Dukeness?
哦 我只是想再看看宝石
Oh, I was just hoping to get another look at the gem
因为它和我的一样
because it's just like mine.
看起来就像巴金堡的宝石
That looks just like the Gem of Barkingburg,
只是它是黄色的！
only it's yellow!
这是一块闪光的宝石
It's the Gem of Flappington.
传说当这两颗宝石结合在一起时
Legend says when the two gems are united,
他们变得无所不能
they become all-powerful.
真正地？强大到足以让某人成为女王？
Really? Powerful enough to, say, make someone queen?
你为什么不打开保险库看看？
Why don't you try to open the vault and find out?
但只有伯爵才能打开保险库
But only the Earl can open the vault
不触发警报
without setting off the alarm.
或者是有个诡计多端的人
Or someone with a very sneaky plan.
像你这样的人 亲爱的？
Someone like you, Sweetie?
帮我拿下巴金堡的宝石
Help me take the gem of Barkingburg
我会和你分享权力和宝座
and I'll share the power and the throne with you.
你将成为女王
You'll be queen.
女王？！成交了！
Queen?! It's a deal!
公主：你非得这么早离开吗？
PRINCESS: Do you have to leave so early?
派对刚刚开始！
The party is just getting started!
我们很快就回来 殿下
We'll be back soon, Your Highness,
给你生日惊喜！
with your birthday surprise!
（警报声）
(Alarm blaring)
联合国警报！警报！是从王座室传来的！
Un alarma! An alarm! It's coming from the Throne Room!
天哪！有人想闯入皇家金库！
Good heavens! Someone is trying to break into the Royal Vault!
（警报响起 关机）
(Alarm blaring, shutting down)
蔡斯：那里！
CHASE: There!
有人从王座室溜出来了！
Someone's sneaking out of the Throne Room!
跟着他！
Follow him!
（吠叫）
(Barking)
我的公主 我刚看见一个小偷跑了
My Princess, I just saw a thief run off
带着巴金堡的宝石！
with the Gem of Barkingburg!
那是不可能的 只有我的声音才能打开保险库！
That's impossible. Only my voice can open the vault!
保险库还关着呢 亲爱的
The vault is still closed, Sweetie.
但我肯定我看到那个拿着宝石的小偷！
But I'm sure I saw the thief with the gem!
巴金堡伯爵
The Earl of Barkingburg.
（叹气）
(Sighing)
傻宝贝 宝石还是安全的
Silly Sweetie, the gem is still safe.
哦 谢天谢地
Oh, thank goodness.
灯怎么了？
What happened to the lights?
♪
哦 不！
Oh no!
现在宝石真的不见了！
Now the gem really is gone!
那贼一定是在灯灭的时候偷偷溜回来的！
The thief must've snuck back in when the lights went off!
哦 天哪 我们必须跑去告诉爪子巡逻队！
Oh dear, we must run and tell the PAW Patrol!
这个计划非常有效！
The plan is working perfectly!
（笑着 哼着气）
(Laughing, snorting)
（吠叫）
(Barking)
住手！
Stop!
\巴金堡公主的名字！
\h\h\hIn the name of the Princess of Barkingburg!
爪子巡逻队 巴尔金堡的宝石
PAW Patrol, the Gem of \h\h\h\h\hBarkingburg
在皇家金库失踪了！
is missing from the royal vault!
我们一定要抓住那个小偷！
We’ve got to catch that thief!
（吠叫）
(Barking)
（喘气）
(Gasping)
♪
他要进入一个秘密通道！
He’s going into a secret \h\h\h\h\h\hpassageway!
（吠叫）
(Barking)
（笑着 哼着气）
(Laughing, snorting)
\他一定是往这边走的！
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hCHASE: He must’ve gone up this way!
（齿轮叮当作响）
(Gears clanking)
嗯？
Huh?
把阿尔金堡的宝石还给我！
Give back the gem of \h\h\h\hBarkingburg!
\h\h\h\h\h阶段：楼梯结束！
\h\h\h\h\hCHASE: The stairs end!
哦哦！
Uh-oh!
哦 不！这是个陷阱！
Oh no! It’s a trap!
我得警告莱德！\h\h\h\h\h\h（尖叫）
I’ve got to warn Ryder! \h\h\h\h\h\h(Screaming)
珍用爪子抓？你在这里干什么？！
Jean-Clawed? What are you \h\h\h\h\h\h\hdoing here?!
（都在喊）
(All shouting)
（琼用爪子尖叫）
(Jean-Clawed screeching)
莱德！我来晚了！
Ryder! I’m too late!
（都在喊）
(All shouting)
跳起来！
Jump!
（都在喊）
(All shouting)
哇！
Whoa!
（喊叫）
(Shouting)
（呻吟）
(Groaning)
哇！
Whoa!
\哈哈！（叮当声）
\h\hWhoa! (Clanking)
（微弱的嘟嘟声）
(Faint beeping)
\我们在哪里？
\h\h\h\hRYDER: Where are we?
听起来他们好像被困在城堡里的某个地方！
It sounds like they’re trapped \h\h\hsomewhere in the castle!
我们一定要找到他们！但是怎么做呢？
We’ve got to find them! But how?
我看见小偷在秘密通道里拉着一根杠杆
I saw the thief pull a lever in the secret passageway.
他知道他们在哪里！
He knows where they are!
你把莱德交给我们的朋友做了什么？
What have you done with Ryder \h\h\h\h\h\h\hand our friends?
（吠叫）
(Barking)
啊！他们应该和其他人一起被抓！
Ugh! They were supposed to be \h\h\htrapped with the others!
没问题 我会用另一种方法把钱给他们！
No problem. I’ll get the drop on them another way!
小心！
Watch out!
好的！如果我不能把他们困在城堡里
Fine! If I can’t trap them \h\h\h\hinside the castle,
我要把他们困在外面！
I’ll trap them outside it!
宝石是我们的
The gem is ours.
（大笑）\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hYeah
(Laughing) \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hYeah.
他走哪条路了？
Which way did he go?
嗯？
Huh?
珠穆朗玛峰：什么？！
EVEREST: \hWhat?!
哦 不！我们怎么回到里面去救莱德和其他人？！
Oh no! How do we get back inside to rescue Ryder and the others?!
（叹气）
(Sighing)
我不能及时警告他们
I couldn’t warn them in time.
我太害怕那只鹰了
I was too scared of that eagle.
没事的 斯凯
It’s okay, Skye.
我们一起把他们弄出来
We’ll get them out together.
我们试着打电话给莱德
Let’s try calling Ryder.
如果我们能找到他 他就能告诉我们他在哪里
If we can reach him, he can tell us where he is.
好主意！珠穆朗玛峰到莱德 \你在那儿吗？
Good idea! Everest to Ryder. \h\h\h\h\h\h\hAre you there?
娜达！没有什么！
Nada! Nothing!
我们得找到一条回城堡的路
We’re going to have to find a \h\hway back into the castle.
哦 它是多么闪耀和闪耀！
Oh, how it sparkles and shines!
（大笑）
(Laughing)
我们的计划成功了 简·克劳德！
Our plan worked, Jean-Clawed!
\宝贝 把巴金堡的宝石给我
\h\hNow give me the Gem of Barkingburg, Sweetie.
你现在应该叫我女王
You should call me Queen now.
好吧 把宝石给我 亲爱的
Fine, give me the gem, \h\h\h\hQueen Sweetie.
都是你的了 现在
It’s all yours. For now.
（大笑）
(Laughing)
♪
（大笑）
(Laughing)
最后！
At last!
看看那个！
Look at that!
这把古老的权杖是用来保存宝石的
This ancient scepter was made \h\h\h\h\h\hto hold the gems.
现在让我们看看他们的\h\h\h\h\h电源能做些什么
Now let’s see what their \h\h\h\h\hpower can do.
哇！
Whoa!
嘿！王座 它是--
Hey! The throne, it’s--
飞行！宝石有让东西飞起来的力量
Flying! The gems have the power to make things fly.
\把权杖给我！轮到我试一试了！
\h\h\h\hGive me the scepter! It’s my turn to try it out!
\我 巴金堡的新国王
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hWhy would I, the new King of Barkingburg,
与你分享我的力量
share my power with you,
一只小狗？
a mere pup?
小狗？你说过我会成为女王的！
Pup? You said I’d be queen!
\把宝石给我！
\h\h\h\h(Growling) Give me that gem!
（咕哝着）
(Grunting)
把它给我！
Give it to me!
（琼用爪子尖叫）
(Jean-Clawed screeching)
♪
啊哈！注意了 乘客们
Ah-hah! Attention, passengers,
您将要进行水上降落
you’re about to make \h\ha water landing.
（喊叫）
(Shouting)
祝你游泳愉快 亲爱的！
Enjoy your swim, Sweetie!
\你怎么敢这样对待未来的巴金堡女王？
\hHow dare you treat the future Queen of Barkingburg like this?
我在飞 珍爪！
I’m flying, Jean-Clawed!
这个接收器有多强大？
Just how powerful is this \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hscepter?
♪
对！我不必统治地面！
Yes! I don’t have to rule \h\h\h\h\h\hon the ground!
我可以成为天空之王！
I can be king of the sky!
（大笑）
(Laughing)
哇！
Whoa!
我要为自己建造一座云中之城！
I’ll build myself a city in the clouds!
但我不能从这张愚蠢的椅子上统治我的领地
But I can’t rule my domain from this silly chair.
啊！我有这个东西！
Ah! I have just the thing!
♪
（咕哝着）
(Grunting)
我们永远过不了这些门
We’ll never get past \h\h\h\hthese doors.
嘘！埃斯库琴！听！
Shh! Escuchen! Listen!
\听到什么了吗！（微弱的嘟嘟声）
\h\h\h\h\h\h\hI hear something! (Faint beeping)
♪
（飞溅）
(Splashing)
他怎么敢把我的王国举起来？！
How dare he lift my kingdom \h\h\h\h\h\h\hinto the sky?!
哇！怎么回事？
Whoa! What’s going on?
光束是从哪里来的？
Where is that beam coming from?
♪
从那只巨鹰那里！
From that giant eagle!
公主！你还好吗？
Princess! Are you all right?
我很好 我的生日聚会变成了一场冒险
I’m fine. My birthday party has turned into quite an adventure.
\我们一定是在一个被遗忘已久的储藏室着陆了
\h\hWe must have landed in a long-forgotten storage room.
爪子巡逻队 报告！
PAW Patrol, report!
追过来！\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h在这里！
Chase here! \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hRocky here!
\在这里！瓦砾在房子里！
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hZuma here! Rubble’s in the house!
我很好！
I’m good!
我是说 是我 马歇尔
I mean, it’s me. Marshall.
所以这意味着斯凯、追踪器和珠穆朗玛峰不在这里
So that means Skye, Tracker and Everest aren’t here.
他们没有在陷阱里被抓住！
They didn’t get caught \h\h\h\h\hin the trap!
也许他们能帮助我们
Maybe they can help us.
斯凯 追踪器 珠穆朗玛峰 你听到了吗？
Skye, Tracker, Everest, \h\h\h\hdo you read me?
没有答案
There’s no answer.
这些超厚的石墙
These super-thick stone walls
一定是挡住了你的信号 莱德
must be blocking your \h\h\h\hsignal, Ryder.
然后我们就得探索房间 寻找出路
Then we’ll have to explore the \hroom and look for a way out.
哇哦哦！
Whoa-oh-oh!
小心 马歇尔！
Look out, Marshall!
抹布像枕头一样柔软！
That wipeout was pillowy soft!
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h（笑）哦 马歇尔
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h(Laughing) Oh, Marshall.
马歇尔 你发现了什么！
Marshall, you found something!
是吗？
I did?
这块石头上有记号！
This stone has markings on it!
祖玛：一扇窗户！事情正在好转 小狗们！
ZUMA: A window! Things are looking up, pups!
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSKYE:整个巴金堡都被升空了！
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSKYE: All of Barkingburg is being \h\h\h\hlifted into the sky!
（哼着）
(Humming)
\h\h\h\h\hDad 巴金堡有飞行汽车吗？
\h\h\h\h\hDad, do they have flying cars in Barkingburg?
（咯咯笑）
(Chuckling)
汽车不能飞 孩子
Cars can’t fly, son.
（喘气）\h\h什么？！
(Gasping) \h\hWhat?!
人们都在那上面的房子里！
People are inside those houses \h\h\h\h\h\hand cars up there!
我们必须帮助他们！
We have to help them!
我们要怎么阻止那只巨鹰呢？
How are we going to stop that \h\h\h\h\hgiant eagle though?
等等 我听到什么了！
Wait, I hear something!
那是引擎的声音！
That’s the sound of an engine!
它是从巨人那里传来的！
It’s coming from the giant \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\heagle!
（发动机轰鸣）
(Engine roaring)
你说得对 追踪器！\那不是鸟
You’re right, Tracker! \h\hThat’s not a bird.
这是一架看起来很像的喷气式飞机
It’s a jet that just looks \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hlike one.
一架巨大的可怕的鹰式喷气式飞机看起来仍然像
A giant scary eagle jet still \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hlooks like
一只可怕的巨鹰！
a giant scary eagle to me!
\我可以从这里看到我的房子！
\h\h\h\h\h\hDUKE: I can see my house \h\hfrom up here!
哦 等等 我是说“你的房子”
Oh, wait. I meant "your house."
♪
啊 这比从王位上统治好多了！
Ahh, this is so much better than ruling from a throne!
呱呱 呱呱！（尖叫声）
Cah-caw, caw! (Squawking)
呱呱 呱呱！谁是天空之王？
Cah-caw, cah-caw! Who is king \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hof the sky?
是我 如果我自己这么说的话 我也是一个很棒的飞行员
It’s me. And I’m also a fabulous pilot if I do say so myself.
我不是吗 珍爪？
Aren’t I, Jean-Clawed?
我看不出是谁从下面飞过来的
I can’t see who’s flying it \h\h\h\h\h\hfrom down here.
哦不 是小狗！
Oh no, it’s the pups!
亲爱的！
Sweetie!
\不是我的错！
\h\h\h\h(Shrieking) It wasn’t my fault!
巴金堡有危险！
Barkingburg is in danger!
莱德和其他人被困在城堡里 你能帮我们吗？
Ryder and the others are trapped in the castle. Can you help us?
等等 你是说你需要我的帮助吗？
Wait, did you say you \h\h\h\hwant my help?
对不起的 我只帮我
Sorry. I only help me.
哦 不！抬头看！
Oh no! Look up there!
那架巨大的鹰喷气式飞机要回来了！
That giant eagle jet is \h\h\h\h\h\hcoming back!
（喘气）
(Gasping)
呵呵？她走了！
Huh? She’s gone!
我们早该知道她有麻烦了
We should’ve known she’d run \h\h\h\h\h\h\hfrom trouble.
让我们看看现在能不能收到信号
Let’s see if I can get \h\h\h\ha signal now.
对！莱德到斯凯 跟踪器\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hand珠穆朗玛峰
Yes! Ryder to Skye, Tracker \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hand Everest.
你能读懂我吗？所有人：是莱德！
Can you read me? ALL: It’s Ryder!
我们到了 莱德！
We’re here, Ryder!
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h是我们！埃斯塔莫斯阿奎伊！
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hIt’s us! Estamos aquí!
（欢呼）
(Cheering)
做得好！
Well done!
莱德 我们被困在城堡外面！
Ryder, we’re trapped outside \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hthe castle!
还有一个坐着巨鹰喷气式飞机的人
And someone in a giant eagle jet
用一个奇怪的光束把巴金堡升空！
is using a strange beam to lift Barkingburg into the sky!
莱德：什么？！\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h（喘息）
RYDER: What?! \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h(Gasping)
不可能！
No way!
我们还被困在城堡里 所以我需要你
We’re still trapped inside the \h\h\h\hcastle, so I need you
把任务巡洋舰带到总部
to take the Mission Cruiser to \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hheadquarters.
所以这是
So this is a...
\霍尔：任务爪子？
\h\h\h\hALL: Mission PAW?
是的！斯凯要去领导它！
Yep! And Skye is going \h\h\h\h\hto lead it!
当铺！\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hYeah！
Pawesome! \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hYeah!
\好吧 好吧！去斯凯！
\h\h\h\h\h\hROCKY: All right! Go Skye!
你想让我来领导任务？
You want me to lead the mission?
\你是我们最有经验的飞行员 我知道你能应付的
\h\hYou’re our most experienced flier, I know you can handle it.
没有一架鹰式飞机太大 也没有一架太小
No eagle jet is too big, \hno Skye is too small.
珠穆朗玛峰 追踪器 斯凯 去总部！
Everest, Tracker, Skye, to \h\hMission Headquarters!
\霍尔：莱德需要我们！
\h\h\h\h\h\hALL: Ryder needs us!
（狂吠 嚎叫）
(Barking, howling)
♪
机器狗 把你的金属放在踏板上
Robo-Dog, put your metal \h\h\h\h\h\hto the pedal
带我们去任务总部
and take us to Mission \h\h\h\hHeadquarters.
（吠叫）
(Barking)
（轮胎吱吱声）
(Tires squealing)
♪
（吠叫）
(Barking)
♪
（吠叫）
(Barking)
赖德？我们准备好任务了
Ryder? We’re mission ready.
谢谢你的催促 小狗们 \我们知道的是
Thanks for hustling, pups. \h\h\hHere’s what we know.
巴金堡的宝石被盗了
The Gem of Barkingburg has \h\h\h\h\h\h\hbeen stolen.
现在有人坐着鹰式飞机
And now someone in an eagle jet
正在把巴金堡升上天空
is raising Barkingburg \h\h\h\h\hinto the sky.
\什么？哦 天哪！
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hBOY: What? Oh my goodness!
小偷可能就是鹰式飞机上的那个人吗？
Could the thief be the same \h\hperson in the eagle jet?
你也许是对的 斯凯
You might be right, Skye.
我们被俘了 你们三个该阻止他了
We’ve been captured so it’s up \h\h\hto you three to stop him
帮助巴尔金堡的人民
and help the people of \h\h\h\h\hBarkingburg.
但是我们怎样才能把他们救到空中呢？
But how are we gonna save them \h\h\h\h\h\hway up in the air?
你已经为这次任务准备了完美的装备
You’ve got the perfect gear for \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hthis mission.
所有新的飞行服和高速喷气机！
All new flight suits and \h\h\h\hhigh-speed jets!
我们要飞了？！
We’re going to fly?!
酷！\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hYes！
Cool! \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hYes!
如果老鹰喷气式飞机驾驶员\h\h\h\h\h\h\h击中我们 赖德？
What if the eagle jet pilot \h\h\h\h\h\hsees us, Ryder?
你的喷气机有一个超级秘密的秘密模式
Your jets have a super secret \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hstealth mode
所以你不会出现在哈尼雷达上
so you won’t be seen on \h\h\h\h\h\hany radar.
追踪器 你的喷气式飞机配备了电缆 所以你可以拉
Tracker, your jet is equipped \hwith cables so you can pull
漂浮的汽车返回地面
the floating cars back \h\h\h\hto the ground.
我要飞去营救！瓦拉雷\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hal重新扫描！
I’ll fly to the rescue! Volaré \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hal rescate!
珠穆朗玛峰 你的喷气式飞机是一只爪子
And Everest, your jet \h\h\h\h\hhas a claw
帮助你营救漂浮建筑物中的任何人
to help you rescue anyone in \h\h\hthe floating buildings.
在空中 珠穆朗玛峰就在那里！
In the air, Everest is there!
斯凯 你需要驾驶你的喷气式飞机去“大鹰”号
And Skye, you’ll need to fly your jet up to the big eagle
阻止任何把巴尔金堡升上天空的人
and stop whoever is raising \hBarkingburg into the sky.
你的意思是我得去喝一杯吗？
You mean I’ll have to get \h\h\h\h\h\h\hclose to it?
我知道你害怕老鹰 但我相信你
I know you’re afraid of eagles, \h\h\h\h\hbut I believe in you.
记住 这是一架喷气式飞机 不是真正的鹰
Just remember, it’s a jet, \h\h\h\h\hnot a real eagle.
可以
Okay...
我们会找到一条离开城堡的路
We’ll find a way out \h\h\h\hof the castle
尽快加入你们
and join you as soon as we can.
好了 任务爪子开始行动！
All right, Mission PAW \h\h\h\his on a roll!
♪
\h\h\h♫爪子巡逻 走 走 走 走∮
\h\h\h♪ PAW Patrol, go, go, go, go, go ♪
✓走 走 走 走♫
♪ Go, go, go, go ♪
（发动机点火）
(Engines firing up)
✓走 走 走 走♫
♪ Go, go, go, go ♪
›爪子巡逻♫
♪ PAW Patrol ♪
我以前从没坐过这架飞机！
I’ve never flown this \h\h\h\h\hfast before!
所以这就是喷气式飞机的速度！
So this is what jet speed \h\h\h\h\h\h\hfeels like!
✓喷气式飞机去救小狗♫
♪ Jet To The Rescue Pups ♪
任务小组！进入\h\h\h\h\hrescue模式
Mission team! Go into \h\h\h\h\hrescue mode,
寻找那些需要帮助的人
and look for people who \h\h\h\h\h\h\hneed help.
我去看看
I’ll go check out that...
（吞咽）鹰式喷气式飞机
(Gulping) Eagle jet.
（吠叫）
(Barking)
\h\h\hBOTH:救援模式！
\h\h\hBOTH: Rescue mode!
♪
✓走 走 走 走♫
♪ Go, go, go, go ♪
♪
啊 今天真是微风习习
Huh, it’s really breezy today.
喔 喔 哦 天哪！
Whoa, whoa, oh my goodness!
等等 女士！
Hold on, Ma’am!
我会让你飞到地上！
I’ll fly you to the ground!
（吠叫）\h\h！
(Barking) \h\hClaw!
♪
（喵喵叫）
(Meowing)
哦 不！
Oh no!
（低吼）
(Yowling)
我抓住你了 基蒂！
I’ve got you, kitty!
（低吼）
(Yowling)
哦！谢谢您！
Oh! Thank you!
看！一只会飞的小狗！
Look! A flying pup!
孩子 小狗不会飞
Pups can’t fly, son.
男孩：耶！
BOY: Yay!
（狂吠）\h电缆！
(Barking) \hCables!
现在出去是安全的
It’s safe to get out now.
谢谢您！
Thank you!
哇！
Whoa!
从空气中看 它看起来更大
It looks even bigger from \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hthe air.
\当飞行员真的很辛苦 停在这里 琼用爪子抓着
\hBeing a pilot is really hard work. Stop here, Jean-Clawed.
我想找点乐子 建立更多我的王国
I want to have some fun and \hbuild more of my kingdom.
（尖叫声）
(Squawking)
很 完美 我的“鹰”雷达上什么也没有
Perfect. Nothing on my eagle \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\heye radar.
天空都是我的
The skies are all mine.
记住莱德说过的话
Remember what Ryder said.
它不是真正的鹰 \他只是一架喷气式飞机
It’s not a real eagle. \h\h\hIt’s just a jet.
我想这已经够近了
I think this is close enough.
现在让我们看看谁在飞这个东西
Now let’s see who’s flying \h\h\h\h\h\h\hthis thing.
呵呵？珍用爪子抓？
Huh? Jean-Clawed?
（大笑）
(Laughing)
\他是公爵！
\h\h(Gasping) It’s the Duke!
看起来
And that looks like...
巴金堡的宝石！
the Gem of Barkingburg!
斯凯给莱德和任务小组
Skye to Ryder and mission team.
去吧 斯凯
Go ahead, Skye.
“鹰”喷气式飞机的驾驶员是小偷哈尔索！
The pilot of the eagle jet is \h\h\h\h\h\h\halso the thief!
是弗拉皮顿公爵！
It’s the Duke of Flappington!
（气喘吁吁地说）
(All gasping)
\我堂兄？我的话！
\h\h\h\h\hMy cousin? My word!
他把宝石放在权杖里
He’s put the gem in a scepter
\汉德正在用它把巴金堡轰上天！
\h\hand is using it to zap Barkingburg into the sky!
那么阻止他的唯一办法就是拿回那颗宝石
Then the only way to stop him is to get that gem back.
你能用钩子抓住权杖吗？
Do you think you could grab the scepter with your hook?
我得飞得离鹰式飞机近一点
I’ll have to fly closer to \h\h\h\h\h\hhis eagle jet
但我会努力的！
but I’ll try!
你能行的 斯凯！
You can do it, Skye!
\我们是来帮你的 队长！
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hEVEREST: We’re coming to help you, \h\h\h\h\h\h\hteam leader!
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h两：（吠叫）隐形模式！
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hBOTH: (Barking) Stealth mode!
我对皇室成员感到震惊
I’m shocked someone from \h\h\h\hthe Royal Family
会有这么不礼貌的
would have such bad manners.
即使他来自远方
Even if he is from a distant branch.
我们得离开这里帮忙 小狗们！
We’ve got to get out of here \h\h\h\h\h\hand help, pups!
\嗨 我想我找到了我们逃跑所需要的东西
\hI think I found just what we need to make our great escape.
别丢了 再用吧！
Don’t lose it, re-use it!
准备好了吗？拉！
Ready? Pull!
（呻吟）
(Groaning)
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h！我们做到了！
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hYay! We did it!
好吧！\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h URRAH！
Alright! \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hHurrah!
大家上去！
Go on up, everyone!
（狂吠 嚎叫）
(Barking, howling)
哇！下一站 护城河！
Whoa! Next stop, the moat!
讨厌！护城河太湿了！
Yuck! Moats are so wet!
哇哦 看看巴金堡！
Whoa. Look at Barkingburg!
（喘气）
(Gasping)
\亲爱的！哦 天哪！
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hOh dear! Oh my!
机器狗 进来
Robo-Dog. Come in.
把任务巡洋舰带回城堡 快点！
Bring the mission cruiser back \h\hto the castle, and hurry!
（吠叫）
(Barking)
我们得把那颗宝石从公爵那里拿走
We’ve got to get that gem away \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hfrom the Duke.
（紧张地吞咽）
(Gulping nervously)
好吧 我进去
Okay, I’m going in.
我就在你后面
I’ll be right behind you.
你是también 我也是
Yo también. Me too.
（吠叫）钩子！
(Barking) Hook!
哦！
Augh!
哦 不！我毁了我们的掩护！我们会见到公爵的！
Oh no! I’ve ruined our cover! The Duke will see us!
（尖叫声）
(Squawking)
什么？
What?
好吧 好吧 好吧
Well, well, well.
三个小飞行员！
Three little pilot pups!
所以你以为你可以偷袭那只大坏蛋？
So you thought you could sneak \h\h\hup on the big bad bird?
琼用爪子抓！激活  \爪子
Jean-Clawed! Activate.. \h\h\h\h\h\h\hthe claws.
\哦哦！留神！
\h\h\h\h\hSKYE: Uh-oh! Look out!
啊 啊 啊！
Ay-ay-ay!
斯凯！公爵抓到我们了！
Skye! The Duke has us!
\哦 不！对不起 团队！
\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSKYE: Oh no! Sorry, team!
这都是我的错！
This is all my fault!
是那只小狗害怕鹰！
It’s that pup who’s afraid \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hof eagles!
别坐在那儿 快点！
Don’t just sit there, come on!
（尖叫声）
(Squawking)
哟呜！这就是你要找的吗？
Yoo-hoo! Is this what \hyou’re looking for?
别担心我们 斯凯！
Don’t worry about us, Skye!
希斯！对！去拿权杖！
Sí! Yes! Go for the scepter!
我怎么才能不靠得太近呢？
How can I get it without getting too close?
也许我闭上眼睛
Maybe if I close my eyes.
你得更努力才能从上面把它弄到手！
You’ll have to try harder to get it from all the way up there!
我就知道她会害怕地飞
Heh, I knew she’d fly \h\h\h\h\haway scared.
那么 吉恩·克劳德 我下一步该怎么去我的王国呢？
So, Jean-Clawed, what should I \h\h\hadd to my Kingdom next?
哦！也许是一个巴克汉堡包\h\h\h\h\h\h餐厅？
Oh! Maybe a Barkingburger \h\h\h\h\h\h\hrestaurant?
所有这些都让我变得非常兴奋 哇！
All this king-ing is making me \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hhungry. Whoa!
我做了吗？我做到了！
Did I do it? I did it!
现在飞离这只鹰！
Now to fly away from this eagle!
别看我 我不会飞！\h\h\h\h\h\h拔出我的权杖！
Don’t look at me, I can’t fly! \h\h\h\h\h\hFetch my scepter!
（尖叫声）
(Squawking)
哦！
Augh!
我丢了！
I lost it!
她跳水太快了！
She’s diving too fast!
停车 斯凯！
Pull up, Skye!
我太低了！
I’m too low!
没有人能阻止天王！
No one can stop the King \h\h\h\h\h\hof the Sky!
（狂笑）
(Laughing manically)
（叹气）
(Sighing)
莱德指望我来完成这次任务
Ryder was counting on me to \h\h\h\h\hlead this mission,
我所做的就是抓住我的团队
and all I did was get my \h\h\h\h\hteam captured.
\威蒂：呃 那个鬼鬼祟祟的公爵拿走了我的宝石！
\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSWEETIE: Ugh, that sneaky Duke \h\hstill has my gem!
嘎嘎！（尖叫声）
Cah-cah-caw! (Squawking)
呱呱 呱呱！（尖叫）
Cah-caw, caw-caw! (Screeching)
（大笑）
(Laughing)
我的王国即将完成
My kingdom is almost complete.
我现在所需要的就是一个国王般的家
All I need now a kingly home \h\h\h\h\h\h\hto rule from.
（咕哝着）
(Grunting)
哇 哇！
Whoa, whoa!
我们离开这里 布兹比！
Let’s get out of here, Buzby!
♪
哦哦！
Uh-oh!
大家 振作起来！
Everyone, brace yourselves!
（隆隆声 爆裂声）
(Rumbling, cracking)
不是城堡！我所有的朋友都在上面！
Not the castle! All my friends \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hare up there!
我本该阻止公爵的
I was supposed to stop the Duke
但我让大家失望了
but I let everybody down.
较高的！较高的！
Higher! Higher!
我想让我的城堡看看
I want my castle to look over
整个王国
the entire kingdom.
哇！这太高了！
Whoa! This is high!
各位 离城堡近一点
Everyone, stay close to \h\h\h\h\h\hthe castle.
救命啊！
Help!
\公主！
\h\h(Gasping) The Princess!
我们得做点什么 布兹比
We have to do something, Buzby.
珠穆朗玛峰 我们得把爪子拔出来！
Everest, we have to get out \h\h\h\h\h\hof these claws!
我在努力 但他们太强大了！
I’m trying, but they’re too strong!
嘎嘎嘎嘎嘎——啊！
Cah-caw-caw-ca-- augh!
\没有人会把我的公主置于危险之中而逃脱惩罚！
\h\h\h\hNo one puts my Princess in danger and gets away with it!
♪
对！我们做到了 布兹比！我们打碎了公爵的横梁！
Yes! We did it, Buzby! We broke the Duke’s beam!
等待！我的飞机怎么了？
Wait! What’s wrong with my jet?
布兹比？！
Buzby?!
看到！杜克王的飞行cas--
Behold! King Duke’s flying cas--
（吱吱声）
(Squeaking)
\什么？！（抱怨）
\h\h\hWhat?! (Grumbling)
这不是你的城堡 也不会去任何地方！
It’s not your castle and it’s \h\h\h\h\hnot going anywhere!
（笑着 哼着气）
(Laughing, snorting)
（欢呼）
(Cheering)
城堡得救了！
The castle is saved!
耶！\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h！
Yay! \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hYes!
听到了吗 布兹比？我知道他们会为我欢呼一天！
Hear that, Buzby? I knew they’d all be cheering for me one day!
（欢呼）
(Cheering)
他们很安全！甜心回来帮忙
They’re safe! Sweetie came \h\h\h\h\h\hback to help.
她并没有从麻烦中逃出来 他就闯了进去！
She didn’t run from trouble, \h\hshe flew right into it!
宝贝拿走了城堡！
Sweetie took the castle \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hI took!
好吧 如果我拿不到它 我会帮我的表弟
Well, if I can’t have it, I’ll \h\h\h\h\hmake sure my cousin
也不能有它！
can’t have it either!
（钟声）
(Clock bonging)
嗯   来吧 我有个好主意
Hm... come on. I have \h\h\h\h\ha big idea.
我是唯一能打败他的人！我必须这么做
I’m the only one left who can \hstop him! I have to do this.
莱德！我要完成这个任务
Ryder! I’m going to complete \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hthis mission,
从让你离开那块岩架开始！
starting by getting you off \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hthat ledge!
我就知道我们可以依靠你！
I knew we could count on you!
\我是斯凯！
\h\h\hALL: It’s Skye!
好吧！对！
All right! Yes!
（吠叫）钩子！
(Barking) Hook!
大家爬上去！
Climb on, everyone!
快点 伙计们！好吧！
Come on, guys! All right!
我们走！哇！
Let’s go! Whoa!
（大笑）
(Laughing)
谢谢 伙计们！
Thanks, dudes!
我们都上船了 斯凯！
We’re all aboard, Skye!
♪
呜呜！谢谢 斯凯！耶！
Woohoo! Thanks, Skye! Yay!
干得好 斯凯！
Well done, Skye!
非常感谢你的搭车！
Thank you so much for the lift!
没问题 现在我要去追那架鹰式飞机！
No problem. Now I’m going after that eagle jet!
（吠叫）
(Barking)
好时机 机器狗！
Good timing, Robo-Dog!
\h\h\h\h\h\hLet要去任务总部 准备好了 孩子们！
\h\h\h\h\h\hLet’s get to Mission Headquarters and gear up, pups!
（吠叫）
(Barking)
好吧 就这样
Okay, this is it.
（尖叫声）
(Squawking)
又是她吗？
Her again?
把我们转过来 我们会一劳永逸地把她吓跑
Turn us around. We’ll scare her off once and for all.
（尖叫）
(Screeching)
（喘气）
(Gasping)
\我在做！我不害怕！
\h\h\hI’m doing it! And I’m not scared!
（狂吠 嚎叫）
(Barking, howling)
现在我要得到一颗宝石和一个公爵！
Now I’ve got a gem to get and a Duke to stop!
让我们看看她有多勇敢
Let’s see how brave she is
当我的其他老鹰来玩的时候
when my other eagles come \h\h\h\h\h\h\hout to play.
打吧 珍爪！
Hit it, Jean-Clawed!
雄鹰无人机！小心 斯凯！
Eagle Drones! Look out, Skye!
他们来找你了！
They’re coming for you!
没问题！
No problem!
♪
也许只是几架无人机
Maybe just a couple \h\h\h\hmore drones.
小心 斯凯！你身后还有更多的人在等着你！
Look out, Skye! There are more \h\h\h\hcoming up behind you!
收到！谢谢 亲爱的！
Copy that! Thanks, Sweetie!
我得甩掉他们
I’ve gotta shake them.
♪
我的尾巴上有这么多无人机 我永远得不到宝石！
I’ll never get the gem with all these drones on my tail!
\嘿 斯凯队长！
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hRYDER: Hey, Team Leader Skye!
看来你可以使用一些空中支援
It looks like you could use \h\h\h\h\hsome air support.
\h\h\h\h\h♫爪子巡逻♫赖德！
\h\h\h\h\h♪ PAW Patrol ♪ Ryder!
我们会处理这些无人机的 你从公爵那里得到宝石
We’ll take care of these drones. You get that gem from the Duke.
我们乘飞机去救援吧！
Let’s jet to the rescue!
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\霍尔：（汪汪）救援模式！
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hALL: (Barking) Rescue mode!
✓走 走 走 走♫
♪ Go, go, go, go ♪
那些讨厌的小狗是怎么从城堡里逃出来的？！
How did those pesky pups escape from the castle?!
为什么他们都有喷气式飞机？
And why do they all have \h\h\h\h\hto have jets?
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\Hyder:小狗们 我把无人机引开 你们把它们团团围住！
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hRYDER: Pups, I’ll lead the drones away and you round ’em up!
罗杰！飞行王牌蔡斯在\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h案件中！
Roger! Flying Ace Chase is on \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hthe case!
（吠叫）绞盘！
(Barking) Winch!
✓走 走 走 走♫
♪ Go, go, go, go ♪
抓住你了！
Got ya!
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hROCKY：让我们回收垃圾吧！
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hROCKY: Let’s recycle the trash!
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hrUBLE:碎石喷射速度加倍！
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hRUBBLE: Rubble on the jet-speed double!
嘿！那些无人机不是\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h！
Hey! Those drones are not \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hgarbage!
\海弗雷斯特！追踪器！准备好做一个涡轮快速突破！
\hEverest! Tracker! Get ready to make a turbo-fast break for it!
\他：（嚎叫）谢谢 斯凯！
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hEVEREST: (Howling) Thanks, Skye!
\谢谢 谢谢！
\h\h\h\hTRACKER: Muchas gracias!
\准备好了 准备好了 开始吧！
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSKYE: Ready, set, let’s jet!
\哦 福伊！
\h\h\hDUKE: Oh, phooey!
我已经准备好迎接一场精彩的比赛了！
I’m ready for a high-flying \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hrescue!
（汪汪）水炮！
(Barking) Water cannon!
›爪子巡逻♫
♪ PAW Patrol ♪
✓喷气式飞机救援⏹
♪ Jet to the rescue ♪
✓走 走 走 走♫
♪ Go, go, go, go ♪
✓喷气式飞机去救小狗♫
♪ Jet To The Rescue Pups ♪
高五 珠穆朗玛峰！
High five, Everest!
真的很高！
Really high!
我所有的小鹰！\啊\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hOne！
All my little eagles! \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hGone!
他们不能这样对我！
They can’t do this to me!
我是天空之王！
I’m the King of the Sky!
\你是国王！
\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSKYE: You aren’t the king \h\h\hof this Skye!
降落你的飞机 把巴金堡的宝石还给我！
Land your jet and give back the Gem of Barkingburg!
让我想想 嗯 不！
Let me think about that. Um. No!
呱呱！珍用爪子抓着 让它跑回家
Cah-caw-caw! Jean-Clawed, send \h\h\h\hthis pup running home
当我照顾城堡的时候
while I take care of the castle.
（钟声）
(Clock bonging)
你不再吓我了！
You don’t scare me anymore!
这只小狗不跑了 它飞了！
And this pup doesn’t run, \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hshe flies!
（尖叫声）\h\h\h\h\h\h太好了！
(Screeching) \h\h\h\h\h\hGot ya!
（困惑地尖叫）
(Confused squawking)
琼用爪子抓！我来抓你！
Jean-Clawed! I’ll get you!
\但是我得先在城堡里放点东西
\h\hBut first I have to drop something off at the castle.
当你玩得开心的时候 时间过得真快
Time flies when you’re \h\h\h\h\hhaving fun.
如果我不能拥有城堡 就没有人能拥有它！
If I can’t have the castle, \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hno one can!
（喘气）哦 不！城堡！
(Gasping) Oh no! The castle!
哇！
Whoa!
哦 不！他要把它扔到城堡上！
Oh no! He’s going to drop it \h\h\h\h\h\h\hon the castle!
（喘着气）\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h！
(Gasping) \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hNo!
时间到了
Time's up.
拜拜巴金堡城堡！
Say bye-bye to Barkingburg Castle!
（大笑）
(Laughing)
跟宝石说再见！
SKYE: Say bye-bye to the gem!
不！
No!
♪
（欢呼）
(Cheering)
这就是我所说的“停止时钟！”
Now that's what I call "stopping the clock!"
好吧 队员们！让我们把大本鸡放回原处！
SKYE: Okay, team! Let's put Big Benji back where it belongs!
马歇尔：好吧！我们做到了！
MARSHALL: All right! We did it!
（嚎叫）
(Howling)
斯凯：殿下 接住！
SKYE: Your Highness, catch!
好极了 斯凯！现在我要拿回我的宝石
Bravo, Skye! Now I'll take back my gem.
（欢呼）
(Cheering)
做国王比做公爵难多了
Being a King was way harder than being a Duke anyway.
吉恩 把我们弄出去
Jean-Clawed, get us out of here.
哦 对
Oh, right.
（尖叫声）
(Squawking)
那个公爵需要被禁足！
That Duke so needs to be grounded!
他要逃跑了！
He's making a run for it!
这个是我的 任务小组 这只小狗要飞了！
This one's mine, Mission Team. This puppy's gotta fly!
又是她？！菲菲 她飞不出去！
Her again?! Pfft, she can't out-fly me!
›爪子巡逻♫
♪ PAW Patrol ♪
✓走 走 走 走♫
♪ Go, go, go, go ♪
我们不能动摇她！全力以赴 让爪！
We can't shake her! Full power, Jean-Clawed!
（尖叫声）
(Squawking)
对！全速前进！
Yes! Full power!
✓走 走 走 走♫
♪ Go, go, go, go ♪
好久不见了 小普 怎么了？！
So long, little pu-uh-uh-- what's happening?!
吉恩·克劳德 我要吊销你的驾驶执照！
Jean-Clawed, I'm taking away your pilot's license!
（尖叫声）
(Squawking)
公爵把发动机推得太猛了 他们会--
The Duke is pushing his engines too hard. They're gonna--
哦 不
Oh no.
（尖叫）
(Screaming)
我来抓你！
I'll get you!
（吠叫）钩子！
(Barking) Hook!
（咕哝着）
(Grunting)
我的引擎在发热！
My engines are heating up!
我再也忍不住了！
I can't hold it much longer!
我做到了！
I did it!
我们在地上？我的鹰式飞机降落了！
We're on the ground? I landed my eagle jet!
我是有史以来最好的飞行员！
I am the best pilot ever!
（尖叫声）
(Squawking)
（大笑）
(Laughing)
♪
哦 你好！我正要出去散散步
Oh. Hello! I was just going for a little walk...
回到Flappington
back to Flappington.
（尖叫声）
(Squawking)
你哪儿也不能去 杜克！
You're not going anywhere, Duke!
除了回巴金堡面对公主！
Except back to Barkingburg to face the Princess!
任务完成了 小狗们！
Mission accomplished, pups!
好吧！令人惊叹的！
All right! Awesome!
我们做到了！（嚎叫）
We did it! (Howling)
干得好 队长斯凯
Outstanding job, Team Leader Skye.
谢谢你相信我 莱德
Thanks for believing in me, Ryder.
一旦我克服了恐惧 我也相信了自己
Once I got over my fears, I believed in me too.
公主 我给你
Princess, I present you with
巴金堡的宝石
the Gem of Barkingburg.
谢谢你 厄尔！看起来怎么样？
Thank you, Earl! How does it look?
它闪闪发光！
It sparkles and shines!
佛朗顿的宝石会怎么样 伯爵？
What's gonna happen to the Gem of Flappington, your Earlness?
它将被存放在皇家金库里
It will be stored in the Royal Vault
让它远离恶作剧者的手
to keep it out of the hands of mischief-makers.
我只会用宝石的力量来保护
I shall only use the power of the gems to protect
我亲爱的巴金堡人民
my beloved people of Barkingburg...
不像我的坏表哥
unlike my badly-behaved cousin.
表弟 我真希望你没拿走我的小东西
Cousin, I do hope you didn't take my little
生日恶作剧真的！
birthday prank seriously!
所有人：恶作剧？！
ALL: Prank?!
我有这个
I've got this.
帮我拿下巴金堡的宝石
Help me take the Gem of Barkingburg
我会和你分享权力和宝座
and I'll share the power and the throne with you.
他想让我和你作对 我的公主！
He tried to get me to work against you, my Princess!
我想说这就是你需要的所有证据 殿下！
I'd say that's all the proof you need, Your Highness!
你不能因为公爵的努力而责怪他
You can't blame a Duke for trying.
我当然可以！但是为了弥补你所做的
Of course I can! But to make up for what you've done,
我会给你一个重新开始的机会
I'll give you a chance to make a clean start in life.
继续打扫 珍爪！我们越快结束
Keep cleaning, Jean-Clawed! The sooner we're done,
我们越快能回到弗拉皮顿
the sooner we can get back to Flappington.
当你看完甜心的小房子后
When you're finished with Sweetie's pup house,
你可以继续你的下一份工作
you can move on to your next job.
擦洗护城河！
Scrubbing the moat!
巴金堡巡逻队 谢谢你
PAW Patrol, all of Barkingburg thanks you
为了拯救王国！
for saving the realm!
（欢呼）
(Cheering)
不客气 公主
You're welcome, Princess.
每当皇室亲戚有什么不好的事 就大声呼救！
Whenever a royal relative is up to no good, just yelp for help!
（大笑）
(Laughing)
站住 小偷！
(Gasping) Stop, thief!
（吠叫）
(Barking)
淘气的宝贝！
Naughty Sweetie!
你知道我不能让你玩巴金堡的宝石
You know I can't let you play with the Gem of Barkingburg.
但作为一个如此忠诚的小狗 换个新的头饰怎么样？
But for being such a loyal pup, how about a new tiara?
我的公主 只知道爪子巡逻队
My Princess, just knowing the PAW Patrol
没有我就不能挽救今天的生活--
couldn't have saved the day without me is reward enou--
哦 太亮了！
Oh, it's so shiny!
说到奖励 向前一步 斯凯！
Speaking of rewards, step forward, Skye!
我？！
Me?!
为了超越职责
For going above and beyond the call of duty,
我首先宣布
I hereby announce you the very first
巴金堡之心骑士！
Knight of the Heart of Barkingburg!
我很荣幸 殿下！
I'm honored, your Highness!
让我们为斯凯听听！小狗 小狗
Let's hear it for Skye! Pup, pup...
大家：万岁！
ALL: Hooray!
厄尔：小狗 小狗！
EARL: Pup, pup!
大家：万岁！
ALL: Hooray!
嘘 斯凯！别忘了公主的生日礼物！
Psst, Skye! Don't forget the Princess's birthday present!
（气喘吁吁）哦 对了！
(Gasping) Oh, right!
♪
最好的生日！
Best birthday ever!
♪